A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Possessions, Series K FA011
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Nelson A. Rockefeller Vouchers, 1934-1958; F.2
  - Art, 2.11
    - Carlebach Gallery, 1953 January-1957 October (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Carlebach Gallery - Coles, William F., 1947 March-1958 November (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Coonradt, Paul - De Nagy, Tibor, 1952 March-1958 August (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - The Downtown Gallery (Box 15, Folder 9)
      Much of the art is paintings, drawings, and sculpture. Downtown Gallery acted as an intermediary between Rainey Bennett and NAR.
    - Dudensing, Valentine - Fine Arts Association, 1943 April-1951 February (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Foinet, Rene Lefebvre - Grand Central Moderns, 1935 June-1958 July (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Grossman, Isadore, 1952 October-1955 January (Box 15, Folder 12)
      Much of the art purchased from Grossman is primitive and native sculpture.
    - Guayasamin, Oswaldo - Harriman, Marie Gallery, Inc., 1935 February-1958 August (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - d'Harnoncourt - Edwin Hewitt Gallery, 1949 July-1957 March (Box 15, Folder 14)
      Much of the art purchased from Edwin Hewitt Gallery is paintings.
    - The House of Heydenryk - Intra-Mar Transport Corp., 1949 March-1958 January (Box 15, Folder 15)
      The House of Heydenryk was responsible for making and repairing frames
    - Marsha Jackson Gallery - W. R. Keating & Co., Inc., 1951 March-1958 July (Box 15, Folder 16)
      Purchases from Sidney Janis Gallery are all paintings. W. R. Keating & Company handled frieght charges.
    - Keck, Sheldon - J. J. Klegman Art Gallery, 1938 September-1957 January (Box 16, Folder 19)
      Much of the art purchased from J. J. Klegman Art Gallery is pre-Columbian and Mexican.
    - J. J. Klegman Art Gallery - Knapp, John Paul, 1950 December-1958 October (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Knoedler, M. & Co. - Kruger, Louise, 1949 January-1958 August (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Laurel Gallery - Maselli, Modesta, 1945 January-1958 October (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Matisse, Alexina - Museum of Indigenous Art, 1947 December-1956 August (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - The Museum of Modern Art, 1947 March-1952 October (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - The Museum of Modern Art, 1953 January-1958 June (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Moore, George B. - Pan American Shop, 1949 October-1958 August (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Betty Parsons Gallery - Old Print Exchange, 1950 December-1958 August (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Parke -Bernet Galleries, Inc. - Povtinari, Candido, 1941 December-1947 December (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. - Scheinman, E., 1935 December-1957 September (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Schempp & Co. - Sowers, Robert, 1952 June-1958 June (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Solde, Pablo - Thannhauser, J. K., 1950 December-1958 August (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Curt Valentin, 1949 November-1952 January (Box 17, Folder 32)
      Also associated with Museum of Modern Art purchases
    - Ve - Wilke, U., 1945 October-1957 January (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - John Wise, Ltd., 1949 December-1950 October (Box 17, Folder 34)
      Many of these purchases are pre-Columbian
    - Yamanaka & Co. - The Zuni Shop, 1934 November-1957 August (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Rockefellers, 2.12
    - Rockefeller, David - JDR Jr. (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Categories of purchases or reimbursements include: Furnishings, Autos, Real Estate, Book Publication Costs, Securities.
    - JDR Jr. (Box 18, Folder 2)
      Categories of purchases or reimbursements include: Personal, Furnishings, Autos, Real Estate, Machinery and Equipment
    - Rockefeller, Nelson to LSR (Box 18, Folder 3)
      Categories of purchases or reimbursements include: Furnishings, Airplane, Art
    - Rockefeller, Nelson to Mary Clark, and Winthrop (Box 18, Folder 4)
      Categories of purchases or reimbursements include: Art, Real Estate, Furnishings, Securities
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. (Box 18, Folder 5)
      Categories of purchases or reimbursements include: Furnishings, Office Alterations, Real Estate
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. (Box 18, Folder 6)
      Categories of purchases or reimbursements include: Alterations, Furnishings, Real Estate
  - Book Publication, 2.13
    - Anderson, Grace V. - Venezuela Basic Corp. (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Authors Include: Grace V. Anderson, Paul Jones, James Monahan, Venezuela Basic Economy Corporation, and others.
  - IBEC, 2.14
    - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) (Box 18, Folder 1-4)
      Includes - Securities, Book Publication costs, Personal, Furnishings, Autos, Chirgua Farm, Hacienda Palo Gordo. IBEC also includes Technical Services Corporation and Housing Corporation.
- Automobiles, general, 1935-1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Automobiles, general, 1955-1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Automobiles, antique cars, Christie's catalog, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Automobiles, Cunningham, 1952-1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Automobiles, De Sotos, 1938-1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Automobiles, Ford, 1931-1936 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Automobiles, Kellner body, 1935-1942 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Automobiles, Lincolns, 1930-1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Automobiles, unsorted, 1935-1958 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Automobiles, Ford Country Squire, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Automobiles, accidents, Carter and Jones Insurance, 1951, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Automobiles, Jaguar, 1949-1951; 1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Automobiles, Mrs. NAR's car, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Awards, general correspondence, 1945-1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Awards, general correspondence, 1960-1971 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Awards, Agricultural Merit Medal (Brazil), 1963 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Awards, Aztec Eagle (Mexico), 1949; 1954 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Awards, Council for the Arts in Westchester (New York), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Awards, Grand Street Boys' Post 1025, American Legion, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Awards, Knickerbocker Hospital, Urban Leadership Award, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Awards, Lord & Taylor Award, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Awards, National Institute of Social Sciences, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Awards, Pythian Diploma, Knights of Pythias, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Awards, Tarrytown/Irvington Chamber of Commerce Man of the Year, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Awards, United Cerebral Palsy Humanitarian Award, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Awards, U.S. Information Agency Distinguished Service Award, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Bassett Hall, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Boats, general, 1944-1947 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Boats, general, 1948-1971 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Boats, Dragon Lady, gift to Florida Institute of Techology, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Boats, Dragon Lady, 1946-1956 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Boats, Dragon Lady, 1961-1968 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Boats, Dragon Lady, Sparkman & Stephens, general, 1956-1969 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Boats, Dragon Lady, Sparkman & Stephens, radar, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Boats, Dragon Lady, Sparkman & Stephens, engines, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Boats, Bull's Eye, 1947-1955 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Boats, charter, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Boats, International L-16 Association, 1965-1971 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Boats, Lloyd's Register of American Yachts, 1948-1966 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Boats, Luders, 1950-1968 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Boats, Queen Mary, 1946-1971 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Boats, Stonington-Dear Island Yacht Basin, 1962-1968 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Boats, Nirvana, 1956-1969 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Boats, Sea Lady (Bertram cruiser), 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Boats, hydrokeel, Anti-Friction Hull Corporation, 1968; 1970; 1970 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Boats, insurance, 1946-1956 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Boats, offers declined, 1939-1946 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Boats, Wayfarer, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Books, general, 1931-1955 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Books, general, 1956-1965 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Books, gneral, 1966-1970 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Books, Ex Libris: catalog of NAR's books, 1948 August (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Books, MoMA and art book inventories, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Books, magazine subscriptions, 1954-1970 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Books, W. 54th Street library, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Books, sent to 13 W. 54th Street (Luncheon Club), 1953-1960 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Books, Washington, DC, 1953-1955 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Books, purchases, 1935-1946 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Cameras, 1965-1971 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- China, Silver, & Glass, Christie's, 1967 February-May (Box 5, Folder 60)
- China, Silver, & Glass, Christie, Manson, 1969 January-March (Box 5, Folder 62)
- China, Silver, & Glass, Christie, Manson, 1969 May-November (Box 5, Folder 63)
- China, Silver, & Glass, Parke-Bernet catalogs, 1965; 1967 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- China, Silver, & Glass, Parke-Bernet catalogs, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- China, Silver, & Glass, Parke-Bernet catalogs, 1969 December (Box 5, Folder 66)
- China, Silver, & Glass, Parke-Bernet catalogs, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- China, Silver, & Glass, Sotheby catalogs, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 68)
- China, Silver, & Glass, Sotheby catalogs, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- China, Silver, & Glass, Sotheby catalogs, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 70)
- Silver, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 71)
- China, Silver, & Glass, J. Rochelle Thomas Inc., 1967-1971 (Box 6, Folder 72)
- China, Porcelain, Antique Company of New York, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 73)
- China, Silver, & Glass, general, lists, 1957-1971 (Box 6, Folder 74)
- China, Silver, & Glass, inventories, 1961-1967 (Box 6, Folder 75)
- China, Silver, & Glass, Seal Harbor inventories, 1949-1961 (Box 6, Folder 76)
- China, Silver, & Glass, Seal Harbor inventories, 1949-1961 (Box 6, Folder 76a)
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2031
- China, Porcelain, Antique Company of New York, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 77)
- China, Porcelain, Antique Company of New York, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 78)
- China, Porcelain, Antique Company of New York, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 79)
- China, Porcelain, correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 7, Folder 80)
- China, Porcelain, correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 7, Folder 81)
- Porcelain, Christie's, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 82)
- Porcelain, Christie's, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 83)
- Porcelain, Sotheby, 1970-1971 March (Box 7, Folder 84)
- Porcelain, Sotheby, 1971 July-December (Box 8, Folder 85)
- Porcelain, Sotheby, 1972 February-May (Box 8, Folder 86)
- Porcelain, Sotheby, 1972 June-November (Box 8, Folder 87)
- China, Porcelain, Furniture, Silver, Sotheby, 1969 December-1970 January (Box 8, Folder 88)
- China, Porcelain, Furniture, Silver, Sotheby, 1970 April-August (Box 8, Folder 89)
- China, Porcelain, Furniture, Silver, Sotheby, 1970 June-August (Box 8, Folder 90)
- China, Porcelain, Furniture, Silver, various, 1970 July-1972 (Box 9, Folder 91)
- China, Porcelain, Sotheby Parke Bernet appraisals, 1976 April (Box 9, Folder 92)
- Degrees, honorary, general, 1943-1970 (Box 9, Folder 93)
- Degrees, honorary, Columbia University, Doctor of Laws, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 94)
- Degrees, honorary, Dartmouth College, Doctor of Laws and Doctor of Civil Laws, 1957, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 95)
- Degrees, honorary, Fordham University, Doctor of Laws, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 96)
- Degrees, honorary, Hamilton College, Doctor of Human Letters, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 97)
- Degrees, honorary, Jewish Theological Seminary, Doctor of Laws, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 98)
- Degrees, honorary, Manhattan College, Doctor of Laws, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 99)
- Degrees, honorary, Michigan State College, Doctor of Laws, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 100)
- Degrees, honorary, Yeshiva University, Doctor of Laws, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 101)
- Fazenda Bodoquena, report translation, 1955 May (Box 10, Folder 102)
- Fazenda Bodoquena, correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 103)
- Fazenda Bodoquena, correspondence, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 104)
- Fazenda Bodoquena, transfer of Nelson Rockefeller's interests to Winthrop Rockefeller, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 105)
- Fazenda Bodoquena, mineral rights, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 106)
- Fazenda Bodoquena, Albion Patterson, 1957-1963 (Box 10, Folder 107)
- Fazenda Bodoquena, cattle, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 108)
- Fazenda Bodoquena, stock transfers and power of attorney, 1956-1967 (Box 10, Folder 109)
- Fifty-fourth floor library/office, general, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 110)
- Fifty-fourth floor library/office, CIAA publications, 1946-1948 (Box 10, Folder 111)
- Finances, general, 1931-1958 (Box 10, Folder 112)
- Finances, general, 1931-1958 (Box 10, Folder 112a)
  Restricted - Living Rockefeller Family - Family Matters - Restricted for Life
- Finances, gifts received from JDR Sr. and JDR Jr., 1909-1950 (Box 10, Folder 113)
- Finances, securities, 1936-1960 (Box 10, Folder 114)
- Finances, securities, 1961-1971 (Box 11, Folder 115)
- Furniture, 1931-1951 (Box 11, Folder 116)
- Furniture, 1952-1969 (Box 11, Folder 117)
- Furniture, Select-a-rest beds, 1960-1966 (Box 11, Folder 118)
- Insurance, general, 1950-1970 (Box 11, Folder 119)
- Insurance, fire, 1948-1959 (Box 11, Folder 120)
- Insurance, Seal Harbor, Maine, house and boats, 1948-1964 (Box 11, Folder 121)
- Insurance, Carter & Jones, Inc., 1947-1953 (Box 11, Folder 122)
- Insurance, Carter & Jones, Inc., 1947-1953 (Box 11, Folder 122a)
  Restricted - Medical records - Open in 2053
- Jewelry, 1931-1971 (Box 11, Folder 123)
- Mayuyama and Co. of Japan, pottery and furniture, 1957-1970 (Box 11, Folder 124)
- Medals, foreign decorations, 1958-1969 (Box 11, Folder 125)
- Medals, foreign decorations, 1958-1969 (Box 11, Folder 125a)
  Restricted - Estate – Nelson A. Rockefeller - Open in 2029
- Music, entertainment systems, general, 1958-1968 (Box 12, Folder 126)
- Music, entertainment systems, Kykuit hi-fi systems, 1956-1966 (Box 12, Folder 127)
- Music, entertainment systems, Boulton stereo guides, 1960-1969 (Box 12, Folder 128)
- Music, entertainment systems, Manhattan Cable Television, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 129)
- "Nelson A. Rockefeller: Portrait of a Man," draft script, 1964 February 14 (Box 12, Folder 129a)
- Photographs, correspondence, 1933-1964 (Box 12, Folder 130)
- Photographs, correspondence, 1965-1971 (Box 12, Folder 131)
- Photographs, Harris & Ewing use of NAR photo, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 132)
- Photographs, Kykuit gallery closet, photo file list, 1969 April (Box 12, Folder 133)
- Photographs, NAR at the Eyrie, Seal Harbor, Maine, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 134)
- Pocantico Oil & Gas Corporation/Pocantico International Corporation, 1962-1969 (Box 12, Folder 135)
- Portraits, artists and offers, 1952-1971 (Box 12, Folder 136)
- Property, Greenrock Corporation, general, 1960-1970 (Box 12, Folder 137)
- Property, Greenrock Corporation, general, 1960-1970 (Box 12, Folder 137a)
  Restricted material - Estate – David Rockefeller - Open in 2042
- Property, Greenrock Corporation, budgets, 1961-1971 (Box 12, Folder 138)
- Property, Greenrock Corporation, budgets, 1961-1971 (Box 12, Folder 138a)
- Property, Greenrock Corporation, employee manuals, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 139)
- Property, Greenrock Corporation, employees, 1946-1964 (Box 12, Folder 140)
  Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2034
- Property, Greenrock Corporation, employees, 1965-1971 (Box 13, Folder 141)
  Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2041
- Property, Greenrock Corporation, NAR letters to retiring employees, 1961-1969 (Box 13, Folder 142)
  Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2039
- Property, Greenrock Corporation employees, Thomas Pyle, 1961-1971 (Box 13, Folder 143)
- Property, Greenrock Corporation, certificate of incorporation and by-laws, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 144)
- Property, Greenrock Corporation, meeting minutes, 1960-1962 (Box 13, Folder 145)
- Property, Greenrock Corporation, meeting minutes, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 146)
- Property, Greenrock Corporation, meeting minutes, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 147)
- Property, Greenrock Corporation, meeting minutes, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 148)
- Property, Greenrock Corporation, meeting minutes, 1966-1971 (Box 13, Folder 149)
- Property, Hills Realty Company, general, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 150)
- Property, Hills Realty Company, general, 1952-154 (Box 13, Folder 151)
- Property, Hills Realty Company, general, 1956-1971 (Box 13, Folder 152)
- Property, Hills Realty Company, inspection and report on property, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 153)
- Property, Hills Realty Company, inspection and report on property, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 153a)
  Restricted material - Living Rockefeller Family - Property - Restricted for Life
- Property, Hills Realty Company, securities held, 1954-1961 (Box 13, Folder 154)
- Property, Hills Realty Company, sale of stock in National Bank of Westchester, 1960 May (Box 13, Folder 155)
- Property, Hills Realty Company, merger of New Rochelle Trust Co. and Peoples National Bank, 1953-1954 (Box 13, Folder 156)
- Property, Hills Realty Company, financial statements, 1960-1961, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 157)
- Property, Hills Realty Company, financial statements, 1964-1966 (Box 14, Folder 158)
- Property, Hills Realty Company, financial statements, 1967, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 159)
- Property, Hills Realty Company, meeting, 1952 October 31 (Box 14, Folder 160)
- Property, Hills Realty Company, meeting, 1963 April 24 (Box 14, Folder 161)
- Property, Hills Realty Company, minutes, 1952-1956 (Box 14, Folder 162)
- Property, Hills Realty Company, minutes, 1957-1970 (Box 14, Folder 163)
- Property, Hills Realty Company, Carlyle Hotel, general, 1953-1967 (Box 14, Folder 164)
- Property, Hills Realty Company, Carlyle hotel, contract and lease, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 165)
- Property, Hills Realty Company, Pocantico village houses, 1967-1971 (Box 14, Folder 166)
- Property, real estate committee, meeting minutes, 1947-1948 (Box 14, Folder 167)
- Property, Hills Western Company, NAR board resignation letter, 1958 December 12 (Box 14, Folder 168)
- Property, Hills Western Company, meeting minutes and agenda, 1955-1961 (Box 14, Folder 169)
- Property, Hills Western Company, railway express property, 1956-1958 (Box 14, Folder 170)
- Property, Hills Western Company, Western Merchandise Mart property, 1953-1956 (Box 14, Folder 171)
- Property, miscellaneous, decorators, 1965-1970 (Box 15, Folder 172)
- Property, miscellaneous, lighting, 1950-1970 (Box 15, Folder 173)
- Property, fallout shelters, general equipment and supplies, 1960-1963 (Box 15, Folder 174)
- Property, fallout shelters, general equipment and supplies, 1960-1963 (Box 15, Folder 174a)
  Restricted material - Estate – Nelson A. Rockefeller - Open in 2029
- Property, fallout shelters, 13 W. 54th Street, New York, NY, 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 175)
- Property, fallout shelters, Governor's Mansion, Albany, NY, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 176)
- Property, fallout shelters, Seal Harbor, Maine, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 177)
- Property, fallout shelters, Tarrytown, NY, 1960-1962 (Box 15, Folder 178)
- Property, fallout shelters, Tarrytown, NY, 1960-1962 (Box 15, Folder 178a)
- Property, fallout shelters, Washington, DC, 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 179)
- Property, real estate owned by NAR, 1964 July (Box 15, Folder 180)
- Property, real estate owned by NAR, 1964 July (Box 15, Folder 180a)
- Property, miscellaneous properties, 1944-1970 (Box 15, Folder 181)
- Property, miscellaneous NYC, 21 W. 53rd Street, MoMA, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 182)
- Property, miscellaneous NYC, 27 W. 53rd Street, 1946-1953 (Box 15, Folder 183)
- Property, miscellaneous NYC, 29 W. 53rd Street, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 184)
- Property, miscellaneous NYC, 5 W. 54th Street, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 185)
- Property, miscellaneous NYC, 9 E. 62nd Street, 1946-1948 (Box 15, Folder 186)
- Property, miscellaneous NYC, E. 68th and 69th Streets at 2nd and 3rd Avenues (Normandy property), 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 187)
- Property, miscellaneous NYC, 123 Greenway North (Queens), 1946-1953 (Box 15, Folder 188)
- Property, 13 W. 54th Street, New York, NY, general, 1946-1966 (Box 15, Folder 189)
- Property, 13 W. 54th Street, alterations and repairs, 1946-1954 (Box 15, Folder 190)
- Property, 13 W. 54th Street, alterations and repairs, 1955-1971 (Box 16, Folder 191)
- Property, 13 W. 54th Street, alarm system, 1960-1964 (Box 16, Folder 192)
- Property, 13 W. 54th Street, elevator repair, 1951-1965 (Box 16, Folder 193)
- Property, 13 W. 54th Street, lease of space to IBEC, 1951-1956 (Box 16, Folder 194)
- Property, 13 & 15 W. 54th Street, New York Steam Corporation, 1951-1955 (Box 16, Folder 195)
- Property, 13 & 15 W. 54th Street, trees, 1953-1967 (Box 16, Folder 196)
- Property, 15 W. 54th Street, acquisition of property by NAR, 1944-1953 (Box 16, Folder 197)
- Property, 15 W. 54th Street, repairs and utilities, 1954-1966 (Box 16, Folder 198)
- Property, 20 W. 55th Street, general, 1951-1958 (Box 16, Folder 199)
- Property, 20 W. 55th Street, general, 1959-1968 (Box 16, Folder 200)
- Property, W. 55th & W. 54th Street buildings, connecting passageway, 1956-1959 (Box 16, Folder 201)
- Property, 22 W. 55th Street, general, 1956-1971 (Box 16, Folder 202)
- Property, 20 and 22 W. 55th Street, general, 1956-1970 (Box 17, Folder 203)
- Property, 22 W. 55th Street, Nesbert Owens (employee file), 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 204)
  Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2030
- Property, 127-129 W. 55th Street, garage, 1946-1967 (Box 17, Folder 205)
- Property, 115 E. 67th Street, apartment, 1930-1935 (Box 17, Folder 206)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, general, 1934-1936 (Box 17, Folder 207)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, general, 1937-1938 (Box 17, Folder 208)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, general, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 209)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, general, 1940-1945 (Box 17, Folder 210)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, purchase, contract with Therese Thorne, 1936-1937 (Box 17, Folder 211)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, alterations by Barr, Iron, & Lane, 1934-1936 (Box 17, Folder 212)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, alterations, general, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 213)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, alterations, general, 1938-1939 (Box 17, Folder 214)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, alterations requisitions #R-1, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 215)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, alterations requisitions #R-2, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 216)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, alterations requisitions #R-3, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 217)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, alterations requisitions #R-4, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 218)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, alterations, remodeling blueprints, 1950 May (Box 18, Folder 219)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, alterations, refurnishing, 1950-1951 (Box 18, Folder 220)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, air conditioning, 1951-1952 (Box 18, Folder 221)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, burglar alarm, 1935-1942 (Box 18, Folder 222)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, cost statements on apartments, 1935-1940 (Box 18, Folder 223)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, elevator, 1952-1958 (Box 18, Folder 224)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, Jean-Michel Frank furniture, 1939-1940 (Box 18, Folder 225)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, glass cases for wall niche, 1956-1959 (Box 18, Folder 226)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, Kellogg, Marie estate (8th floor), 1952 (Box 18, Folder 227)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, McGowan, Herbert, elevator operator, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 228)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, water damage, 1947-1952 (Box 18, Folder 229)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, building matters, 1934-1952 (Box 18, Folder 230)
- Property, 810 Fifth Avenue, building matters, 1954-1971 (Box 18, Folder 231)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue, general, 1961-1964 (Box 19, Folder 232)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue, general, 1965-1971 (Box 19, Folder 233)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue, general, 1965-1971 (Box 19, Folder 233a)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue, blueprints and plans, 1961-1965, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 234)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue, interior furnishings, 1949, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 235)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue, interior furnishings, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 236)
- Property, 810-812 Fifth Avenue, interior furnishing orders, 1963-1972 (Box 19, Folder 237)